STANDARD FOR LIFE
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You are the reason I live
You're the One for me
Why should I fear when I have You
Surrounded by Your love
Your everlasting love
Why should I care what people say
They don't know what You mean to me
Oh, You are the reason
You are the reason I live
You're the One for me
Why should I fear when I have You
Surrounded by Your love
Your everlasting love
Why should I care what people say
They don't know what You mean to me
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Thank you. You may be seated.
Hallelujah!
Viewers all over the world — I want to give you a salute for your faith.
Thank you for your time.
Hallelujah!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Yes, we shall go ahead as the Spirit direct.
I was with you — what a wonderful testimony
You have seen the reason to believe Jesus — He is reliable.
I say Jesus is reliable.
Amen!
I can't hear you.
He is reliable.
I say He is reliable.
If you rely on Him, He will not disappoint you.
He will not fail you; He is not a man.
He is not a man.
He is reliable.
Hallelujah!
If you know that He is reliable, what you need to do is to confess what is in your heart.
When you read the Bible from Genesis to Revelation,
when you confess what is in your heart, Jesus comes in to bring the balance.
Take your pen and write.
When you confess what is in your heart, Jesus comes in to bring the balance.
You know He is reliable. Now, it is time to believe Him.
You have seen He is reliable.
You can rely on Him.
If you know that He is reliable, it is time to confess what is in your heart.
When you confess what is in your heart, Jesus comes in to bring the balance.
It means that when you confess what is in your heart, the job is half done -
fifty-fifty.
Fifty from your side, fifty from His side.
It is not totally Him.
I know it is a strange teaching to you.
Viewers, listen again.
It is fifty-fifty.
This is why you cannot just walk in and receive.
That’s why you cannot just after you have taken drugs or groaned, receive the blessing.
Your faith is needed.
You have a role to play.
It is fifty-fifty.
How?
When you confess what is in your heart, the job is half done.
Tell your neighbour:
I can't hear you clearly.
When you confess what is in your heart, the job is half done.
When you confess what is in your heart, Jesus comes in to bring the balance.
And what is the balance? Fifty.
From your own side - fifty.
His own side is there automatically.
It is available.
It is that the anointing is more than the demand.
So it is fifty-fifty.
To now confess what is in your heart is the problem.
Everything you are saying, "Jesus, Jesus" - you are just speaking with your lips.
You are not sincere.
You have not been sincere.
When you confess what is in your heart, the job is half done.
That is fifty percent.
Now, the remaining fifty percent - Jesus automatically comes in to bring the balance.
It is not all up to Him; certainly it is not all up to you.
Your genuine willingness plus His ability to change.
Your genuine willingness, which is fifty percent,
His own ability to change, which is fifty percent. Fifty plus fifty.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Your genuine willingness.
Not just willingness but genuine willingness.
It must involve your future.
That what I’m saying now, I mean it for tomorrow.
What I’m saying now, I mean it for the day after tomorrow.
What I’m saying, I mean it forever.
I will follow you Jesus.
Not just today - when there’s money in the pocket and when there’s no money in the pocket.
That is, confess what is in your heart.
MESSAGE TITLE: MATCH YOUR ACTION WITH YOUR WORDS
When we say; "To confess what is in our heart", it has to do with your present and your future.
Your present - now, and your future.
This means heart.
Heart mean present, future.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Whether, in the future, there will be money in the pocket,
whether there will be no money in the pocket,
there will be food on the table or no food on the table.
That is heart.
For God to say, "A man of my own heart".
He is not only considering the present of David,
He is not considering the past of David,
but He is considering his future.
Let someone say, "A man of my own heart".
A man of my own heart.
I can’t hear you.
So for you to know what the word heart means.
Faith is of man’s heart.
Heart mean spirit, that is your spirit.
Not literal meaning.
In your school, it is not regarded like that.
Biblically, heart is spirit of man.
You can call it heart or you can call it spirit;
you can call it faith of man’s heart or you can call it faith of man's spirit.
Heart has to do with now and next -
what you will be doing now, what you stand for now,
is what you are going to start from tomorrow.
Heart.
When you confess what is in your heart, the job is half done.
Let someone say that.
If you stand before me and say,
"T.B. Joshua, I’m not well and I’m a man of God’s heart",
that is someone who obeys God, listens to God - I will help you.
But the way you now tell me a different thing, whereas it is not that,
"T.B. Joshua, I don’t have money!" - whereas you have money.
I may likely not be able to meet your need
because you have not met the fifty percent requirement.
MESSAGE TITLE: MATCH YOUR ACTION WITH YOUR WORDS
Are you with me?
A man of my own heart.
That is, when you confess what is in your heart, the job is half done.
It means that if you just confess what is in your heart – "I need bread" -
and God does not give you that bread,
yet He is aware you have no bread,
He will protect you, cover you and be with you.
Fifty percent is okay.
In a neutral meaning - in a school, when you score fifty percent, you will get a pass mark.
It means that if you now confess God and seek what is exactly in your heart,
and you do not receive that healing,
He will be with you through that trial time until you will receive.
Because he is aware you are sick.
The heart is very important
because the Bible says, "Christianity lies in the heart".
Let someone say that.
Christianity lies in the heart.
I can’t hear you.
Yes. Christianity lies in the heart.
If many of us had known this for a long time, you would have worked out things better than this.
If I confess what is in my heart, the job is half done, I will score fifty percent.
If you now confess what is in your heart, "Lord, I’m sick. I have a headache!"
and you do not receive healing,
He will still be with you throughout the trial of that pain until you receive.
He is aware.
When God is aware of your situation, don’t bother.
The situation cannot kill you any longer.
The situation cannot destroy you any longer.
Your struggle will make you stronger.
It will not impair you but improve you.
The words — confess what is in your heart — mean: Match your action with your words.
Let someone say that.
Match your action with your words.
Match your action –
that is, what you are saying is what you are doing.
What you are saying is what you are doing.
It means that your words match with your action.
Match your action with your words means to confess what is in your heart.
What you are saying is what you are doing.
To summarise my message today:
Match your action with your words means to confess what is in your heart -
the job is half done.
Then, Jesus comes in to bring the balance.
What is the balance? Fifty percent.
Let me talk to the viewers.
Sometimes, they want me to talk to them.
They want me to face them.
All what I’m saying now, somebody would say, "Face us!
You are talking to your people here. Face us!"
Now I want to face you to tell you what I am talking about.
Viewers, thank you very much.
I don’t know the position you are in
and whatever situation you are facing - Jesus knows better.
I want to tell you right now - this is a revelation for you.
Some of us didn't know about this in the past.
But revelation is ahead of us.
We are here, revelation is there.
We have to look into revelation to receive.
Speak what is in your heart.
Like I have said in my message that faith is of man’s heart.
When we say, faith is of man’s heart, we mean faith is of man’s spirit.
When you say heart, you mean spirit.
Speak what is in your heart - the job is half done.
When you speak what is in your heart, Jesus comes in to bring the balance.
If you still haven't received that thing, it means Jesus is aware of your situation.
When Jesus is aware, it is like He has solved your problem.
There is no difference between Jesus being aware of your situation and solving your problem.
Solving your problem and being aware of your problem is the same.
If I have leg pain and I run to Jesus, "Help me! Help me!"
and Jesus says, "I will help you!",
He is aware of my leg pain. It is as good as helping me.
If He is aware of my leg pain and He has not helped me,
He has not healed me and I still have that leg pain but He is aware -
it is as good as helping me.
If He is aware of your situation, your situation becomes His situation:
Your pain becomes His pain.
By His stripes, He helps and delivers us.
Viewers, speak what is in your heart.
Speak what is in your heart.
When you speak what is in your heart and say, "Jesus", He comes to the scene immediately -
instantly, He comes to the scene.
This is the revelation for us today.
You just write it down
This is what we mean by "Match your action with your words".
Match your action with your words.
What you say should be what you are doing.
Thank you. God bless you.
Hallelujah.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.